

## CONTACT

- +37067576067
- dmitrij.purynzin@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/dmitrij-purynzin/
- https://purynzin.vercel.app/

## **EDUCATION**

09/2023 - 06/2024
VILNIUS VOCATIONAL TRAINING
CENTRE OF TECHNOLOGIES

JavaScript programmer modular vocational training programme

09/2018 - 06/2021 VILNIUS UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES

Creativity and Business Innovations

#### **SKILLS**

- JavaScript (ES6)/TS
- React.js
- Express.js/Nest.js
- SQL
- Git
- Sass
- MongoDB/mongoose

### LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Lithuanian (Native)
- Russian (Fluent)

# **DMITRIJ PURYNZIN**

JAVA INTERN || JAVASCRIPT STUDENT

#### **PROFILE**

I am 25 years-old and at the right moment studying JavaScript programmer modular vocational training program at Techin. I proudly serve as a member of the Lithuanian National Defense Volunteer Forces. I perfectly handle Lithuanian, Russian, and English languages.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

**UAB "Edrana Baltic"** 

Java Developer Intern

04/2024 - PRESENT

Experience in Java and JavaScript development, focusing on product development involving database management with RDBMS using SQL

**Allen and Coles Moving** 

04/2023 - 08/2023

Crew Member

Working in this company I improved my time management, driving skills, working in team, enhanced problem-solving

**Lithuanian Armed Forces** 

03/2021 - PRESENT

Military Volunteer Forces

While being here I'm improving leadership, teamwork, communication, problem-solving, discipline and stress management

**UAB "Sanremos"** 

10/2016 - 04/2020

Bartender/Administrator

I gained experience in customer service, documentation and inventory management